asianrice.tv 2015-05-31

# AsianRice.TV - Online source for free asian streaming video

AsianRice.TV Privacy Policy

AsianRice.TV is committed to protecting your privacy. AsianRice.TV does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. AsianRice.TV will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following contains details on how we treat all information collected on AsianRice.TV 

BY USING AND/OR VISITING THIS WEBSITE (collectively, including all Content available through the AsianRice.TV domain name, the "AsianRice.TV Website", or "Website"), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO TERMS OF USE, WHICH ARE PUBLISHED AT http://www.asianrice.tv/index.php?section=terms, AND WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the AsianRice.TV Website. 

Any User can use AsianRice.TV without having a AsianRice.TV Account or any other Account. 

We may record information about your usage, such as when you use AsianRice.TV, how many times you visit the website and other non-personal identifiable information. 

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through AsianRice.TV, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of AsianRice.TV, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major AsianRice.TV changes). 

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of AsianRice.TV and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications. 

We use cookies and log file information to:   
(1) provide custom, personalized content and information;   
(2) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns;   
(3) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, time on site, bounce rate, etc... 

Any link that you voluntarily send us becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

AsianRice.TV allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within AsianRice.TV. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on AsianRice.TV. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

AsianRice.TV does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
